Mittenthal, Richard Papers 6407
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Bay City Michigan through Buckeye Florida, 2002-2011 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Bowater Incorporated, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    10/6/2008
  - Item 6: Bridgestone/Firestone Incorporated, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    11/27/2002
  - Item 7: Bridgestone/Firestone Incorporated, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    6/29/2004
  - Item 8: Bridgestone/Firestone Incorporated, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    1/29/2006
  - Item 9: Bridgestone/Firestone Incorporated, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    7/6/2006
  - Item 10: Buckeye Florida Regiional Transportation, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 7)
    3/14/2011
- Central Florida Regional Transportation through CSC Ltd, 1997-2011 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Central Florida Regional, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    5/21/2007
  - Item 2: Central Florida Regional, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    4/16/2010
  - Item 3: City of Chicago (Police), 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    4/1/2010
  - Item 4: City of Cocoa, Florida (firefighters), 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    2/27/2007
  - Item 5: Cheboygan Road Commission, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    12/8/2009
  - Item 6: City of Columbus (fire department), 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    7/29/2004
  - Item 7: Comcast of Alabama, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    11/20/2005
  - Item 8: Consumer's Energy, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    7/22/2004
  - Item 9: Consumer's Energy, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    1/17/2007
  - Item 10: Consumer's Energy, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    8/18/2011
  - Item 11: Consumer's Energy, 2012; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    3/15/2012
  - Item 12: Continental Deli Foods, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    1/1/2004
  - Item 13: C Lec Cook - Dover Resouces, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    1/14/2004
  - Item 14: Corn Bolt Energy, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 8)
    6/9/2010
- DeLand Florida through 34th District Court, 2005-2009 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Cit of Deland, Florida Police, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    1/7/2009
  - Item 2: City of Deltona, Florida - firefighters, 2012; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    1/23/2012
  - Item 3: Detroit Edison, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    4/26/2006
  - Item 4: Detroit Edison, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    5/10/2006
  - Item 5: Detroit Edison, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    12/19/2006
  - Item 6: Detroit Edison, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    11/11/2008
  - Item 7: Detroit Edison, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    2/9/2009
  - Item 8: Detroit Edison, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    2/25/2009
  - Item 9: Detroit Edison, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    4/2/2009
  - Item 10: Detroit Edison, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 9)
    11/12/2009
- Electrolux Home Products through City of Hollywood, 2003-2011 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Electrolux Home Products, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    6/7/2006
  - Item 2: Charter Township of Flint, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    10/17/2006
  - Item 3: University of Floida - Housing Department - Gainsville, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    5/3/2010
  - Item 4: Formula Corp, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    6/6/2010
  - Item 5: GDX Automotive NA, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    2/10/2009
  - Item 6: Georgia - Pacific Corp Epic Plant, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    10/21/2003
  - Item 7: Gogebic Medical Care Faculty, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    3/4/2009
  - Item 8: Goodrich, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    2/23/2011
  - Item 9: Grand Rapids Gravel, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    8/15/2006
  - Item 10: Heidelberg Distributing Company, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    8/17/2010
  - Item 11: City of Hollywood Fire/Rescue/Board, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 10)
    12/11/2003
- Innovative Telephone through Lenawee Health Alliance, 2002-2011 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Innovative Television, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    12/3/2003
  - Item 2: Insituform Technologies, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    3/4/2004
  - Item 3: City of Oren, Mt - Police, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: City of Ironwood, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    4/7/2010
  - Item 5: J & L Specialty Steel, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    7/17/2003
  - Item 6: Jacksonville Electric Authority, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Johnstown Specialty Castings, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    12/2/2008
  - Item 8: KM Plant Services, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    9/14/2004
  - Item 9: Koppers Industries, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    11/3/2004
  - Item 10: Kroger, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    8/11/2011
  - Item 11: Kroger, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    5/9/2007
  - Item 12: Lake City Area Schools, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    4/14/2011
  - Item 13: Leclanau County Sheriff, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    4/28/2011
  - Item 14: Leclanau County Sheriff, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    11/18/2009
  - Item 15: Lean Corporation, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    12/13/2006
  - Item 16: Lenaivee Health Alliance, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 11)
    6/5/2007
- McLaren Regional Medical Center through Muskegon County Board, 2003-2010 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Mc Laren Regional Medical Care, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    3/23/2004
  - Item 2: Mead/West VACO, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    11/23/2004
  - Item 3: Means Industries, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    9/10/2008
  - Item 4: Miami Dade - Metropolital Dade Transportation, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    6/29/2010
  - Item 5: State of Michigan - Office of State Employees, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    11/29/2010
  - Item 6: Regents of University of Michigan, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    12/2/2003
  - Item 7: Minute Men & MFG company, 2013; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    12/1/2013
  - Item 8: Muskegon County Board of Commerce, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    1/9/2008
  - Item 9: Muskegon County Board of Commerce, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 12)
    1/26/2009
- Nashville Gas through Northern Indiana Public Service, 2000-2011 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Nashville Gas Company, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 13)
    5/12/2004
  - Item 2: New Center Community Mental Health, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: National Army Medical Department, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 13)
    5/5/2011
  - Item 4: Norfolk Southern Corporation, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Norfolk Southern Railway Company, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 13)
    2/27/2004
- Northern Indiana Public Service through Phillip Morris, 2005-2011 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 1998; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    8/21/1998
  - Item 1: Packaging Corporation of America, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    3/9/2005
  - Item 2: Perfection Associate, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    3/7/2011
  - Item 2: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    3/30/2000
  - Item 3: Charter Township of Plymouth, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    2/1/2008
  - Item 3: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    9/19/2006
  - Item 4: Phillip Morris, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    12/13/2007
  - Item 4: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    11/25/2003
  - Item 5: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    2/24/2004
  - Item 6: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    10/17/2005
  - Item 7: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    11/2/2005
  - Item 8: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    11/15/2006
  - Item 9: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    11/14/2005
  - Item 10: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    12/22/2005
  - Item 11: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    8/16/2006
  - Item 12: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    7/1/2007
  - Item 13: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    8/1/2007
  - Item 14: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    11/6/2007
  - Item 16: Northern Indiana Public Services Company, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    10/14/2010
  - Item 17: Northpoint Senior Services, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    4/21/2009
  - Item 18: Northwest Airlines, 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 14)
    5/16/2006
- Railway Labor Act through Stewart-Sutherland, 1996-2010 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Report to President by Emergency Board, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Raybestos Products Company, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    11/28/2000
  - Item 3: Repair Industries of Michigan, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    4/26/2010
  - Item 4: SBC Southwestern Bell Yellow Pages, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    11/11/2004
  - Item 5: Schutte Metal Furnishings, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    4/12/2004
  - Item 6: Sodexho Cuttentor Hospital, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    2/7/2007
  - Item 7: Southen Belle Dairy, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    12/17/2010
  - Item 8: City of of Southfield Firefighters Association, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    5/3/2000
  - Item 9: Spartan Stores, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 15)
    9/22/2009
- City of Tallahassee through Troy School District, 1998-2011 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Stewart Southerland Incorporated, 2003; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: City of Tallahassee (Police), 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    8/27/2004
  - Item 3: City of Tampa Fire Department, 2010; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    10/7/2010
  - Item 4: Temple Inland Company (Steelworkers), 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    11/3/2009
  - Item 5: Tinken Company Harison Steel Plant, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    11/27/2005
  - Item 6: Toledo Edison Company 3/17/04, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    3/17/2004
  - Item 7: City of Toledo, Ohio (Police Association), 2006; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: Tower Automotive, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    1/27/2005
  - Item 9: Trance Company (Auto), 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    5/10/2004
  - Item 10: Transmontaige Services, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    11/25/2009
  - Item 11: Troy School District, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 16)
    4/13/2011
- Unicare Life and Health Insurance through Worley Parsons Constructors, 2002-2009 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Unicare Life & Health Insurance Company, 2004; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 17)
    8/3/2004
  - Item 2: Union Pacific Railroad Company Case #1, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 17)
    11/4/2001
  - Item 3: United Airlines (Pilots), 2002-2006 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: U.S. Postal Service, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 17)
    9/22/1989
  - Item 5: WCI Steel, 2005; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 17)
    12/14/2005
  - Item 6: WCI Steel, 2008; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 17)
    7/7/2008
  - Item 7: Wexford Health Services, 2007; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 17)
    6/20/2007
  - Item 8: Worley Paisons Constructions, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 3, Folder 17)
    11/17/2009
- Allegheny Ludlum, 1959-2005 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Bridgestone/Firestone, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 1-20, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 21-40, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 41-64, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 65-92, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 93-118, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 119-149, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 150-171, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 172-195, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 196-220, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 221-243, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 244-263, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Copperweld Steel Decisions 264-278, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- CSC Limited, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Crucible Steel Decisions RM-1 - RM23, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Crucible Steel Decisions RM-24 - RM-43, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Crucible Steel Decisions RM-44 - RM-60, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Great Lakes Steel Decisions, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Great Lakes Steel Decisions, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Great Lakes Steel Decisions, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Great Lakes Steel Decisions, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Decisions, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Decisions, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Decisions, 1980; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Decisions, 1981; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Decisions, 1982; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Decisions, 1983; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Jones and Laughlin Steel Arbitration Rules of Procedure, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 4, Folder 23)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1985; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 1)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1986; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 2)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1987; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 3)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1988; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 4)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1989; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 5)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1990; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 6)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 7)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 8)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1993; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 9)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1994; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 10)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1995; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 11)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 12)
- LTV Steel Decisions, 1997; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Northern Indiana Public Service Decisions, 1994-2005 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Republic Steel Decisions 201-224, 1959; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Republic Steel Decisions 225-247, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Republic Steel Decisions 228-247 (copy 2), 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Republic Steel Decisions, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Republic Steel Decisions, 1963; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Republic Steel Decisions, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Republic Steel Decisions, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Republic Steel Decisions, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- US Steel Atlantic City Ore Decisions, 1966; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 23)
- US Steel American Bridge Decisions, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- US Steel Duluth Works Decisions, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 25)
- US Steel Fairless Works Decisions, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- US Steel Gary Works Decisions, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- US Steel Geneva Works Decisions, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- US Steel Great Lakes Fleet Decisions, 1972-1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- US Steel Homestead Works Decisions, 1969-1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- US Steel Irvin Works Decisions, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 31)
- US Steel Joliet-Waukegan Works Decisions, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 5, Folder 32)
- US Steel Lorain-Cuyahoga Works Decisions, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- US Steel Michigan Limestone Decisions, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- US Steel Minnesota Ore Decisions, 1967-1976 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- US Steel National-Duquesne Works Decisions, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- US Steel Oliver Iron Mining Decisions, 1961-1964 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- US Steel Pension Fund Decisions, 1979; Arbitration Case (Box 6, Folder 3)
- US Steel Pittsburgh Works Decisions, 1966-1977 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- US Steel South Works Decisions, 1968-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- US Steel Supply Division Decisions, 1964-1977 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- US Steel Universal Atlas Cement Decisions RM1 - RM23, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- US Steel Universal Atlas Cement Decisions RM24 - RM 51, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- US Steel UAC-Buffington Decisions, 1978; Arbitration Case (Box 6, Folder 9)
- US Steel Youngstown Works Decisions, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Wheeling-Pittsburg Steel Decisions RM1 - RM20, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Wheeling-Pittsburg Steel Decisions RM21 - RM41, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- White Pine Copper Decisions, 1969-1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM1 - RM20, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM21 - RM40, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM41 - RM60, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM61 - RM80, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM81 - RM100, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM101 - RM120, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM121 - RM140, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM141 - RM160, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM161 - RM180, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM181 - RM200, 1974; Arbitration Case (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM201 - RM220, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM221 - RM240, 1975; Arbitration Case (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM241 - RM260, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM261 - RM280, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM281 - RM300, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM301 - RM320, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM321 - RM340, 1977; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Youngstown Sheet and Tube Decisions RM341 - RM364, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Allis-Chalmers Decisions, 1969; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Allis-Chalmers Decisions, 1970; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Allis-Chalmers Decisions, 1971; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Allis-Chalmers Decisions, 1972; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Allis-Chalmers Decisions, 1973; Arbitration Case (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Allis-Chalmers Decisions, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Caterpillar-Tractor Decisions, 1961-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 1-20, 1956-1959 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 21-40, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 41-60, 1963-1969 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 61-80, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 81-100, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 100-120, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 121-140, 1984-1990 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Dana Corporation Decisions 141-159, 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Doehler-Jarvis Decisions 1-20, 1966-1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Doehler-Jarvis Decisions 21-40, 1973-1978 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Doehler-Jarvis Decisions 41-60, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Doehler-Jarvis Decisions 61-75, 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Volkswagen Decisions RM1 - RM8, 1982-1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- American Postal Workers Union Decisions, 1974-1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- American Postal Workers Union Decisions, 1983-1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- American Postal Workers Decisions, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- National Association of Letter Carriers Decisions, 1975-1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- National Association of Letter Carriers Decisions, 1982-1990 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- National Association of Letter Carriers Decisions, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- APWU and NALC Decisions, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- APWU and NALC Decisions, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- APWU and NALC Decisions, 1991; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 9)
- APWU and NALC Decisions, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Laborers International Union of North America Decisions, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- National Rural Letter Carriers Decisions, 1976; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Eastern Airlines Decisions, 1974-1983 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- United Airlines Decisions, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- CSX Transportation, 1992; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 15)
- National Carriers-Conference Committee, Emergency Board No.230, 1996; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Amtrak, 1998-2002 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Burlington Northern Railroad Decision, 1999; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Consolidate Rail Corporation (Conrail) Special Board of Adjustment No.1123, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 19)
- National Railroad Passenger Corp., Amtrak, 2000; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Norfolk Southern Railway, Hollidaysburg Car Shops, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Norfolk Southern Railway, New York Dock Protection, 2001; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 22)
- National Railroad Adjustment Board, 3rd Division, Awards 36280-36320, 2002; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Norfolk Southern Railway, Special Board of Adjustment, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- National Railroad Adjustment Board, 3rd Division, Decisions, 2012; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Anheuser-Busch, 1986-1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Boston University, 1981-1986 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Consumers Energy, 1959-2001 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Deltona Florida Special Magistrate Report, 2012; Arbitration Case (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Detroit Edison, 1988-2005 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Detroit Free Press, 1969-1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Evening News Association, 1970-1997 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- General Dynamics, 1978-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- General Electric, 1983-1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Greyhound Lines, 1982-2001 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- National Football League, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Trane Company Decisions, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Vistar of Carolinas Decisions, 2009; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Walt Disney Decisions, 2011; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Agency for International Development Decisions, 1980-1985 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Department of State Decisions, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Department of State Decisions, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- US Information Service Decisions, 1984; Arbitration Case (Box 9, Folder 7)
- US International Communication Agency Decisions, 1978-1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)